RG 005:033, Office of the Governor: Abraham Ribicoff (1955-1961)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 9. Press Files
  - Inaugural Address Material, 1959 (Box 699)
  - Increased [State] Services (Box 699)
  - Industrial Management Assoc[iation], New Britain, YMCA (Box 699)
  - Industry – Belding, Heminway, Coticelli – Putnam, Conn[ecticut] (Box 699)
  - Industry – Bigelow Sanford (Box 699)
  - Industry – Connecticut (Box 699)
  - Industry – Connecticut Company (Box 699)
  - Industry – Conn[ecticut] Development Credit Corp[oration] (Box 699)
  - Industry – Dardick Corporation, Hamden, Conn[ecticut] (Box 699)
  - Industry – Escambia Chemical Corporation, Wilton, Conn[ecticut], 1958 October 17 (Box 699)
  - Industrial Expansion (Box 699)
  - Industries Moved Out of State, 1955-1959 (Box 699)
  - Industry – New, 1959 (Box 699)
  - Industry – New – Mosler Safe Co[mpany] (Box 699)
  - Industry – New Man[u]f[acturin]g Industries in Conn[ecticut], 1955-1959 April 13 (Box 699)
  - Industry – Soundscriber Corp[oration] (Box 699)
  - Industry – U[nited] S[tates] Finishing – Aspinook Plant, Norwich (Box 699)
  - Insurance – Automobile Rate Increase (Box 699)
  - Insurance – Automobile Rebate (Box 699)
  - Insurance Tax, General Assembly Statistics, etc. Veto Message (Box 699)
  - Insurance Tax, General Assembly, 1957 session (Box 700)
  - Inter-State Commission (Box 700)
  - Iowa (Box 700)
  - Israel [Draft of Remarks Given by Governor Ribicoff for Radio Program Produced by the American Committee for Israel’s Tenth Anniversary Celebration, tape, 1958 March 26 (Box 700)
  - Jackson-Jefferson Dinner Manchester, N[ew] H[ampshire], Manchester], 1959 October 24 (Box 700)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 1956-1957 (Box 700)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, ( Hotel Statler), 1958 March 8 (Box 700)
  - Jewett, Cha[rle]s W. (L[ieutenan]t Gov[ernor]) (Box 700)
  - Johnson Case [Major Wilfred X.] [Governor’s Military Aide], 1956 February-April (Box 700)
  - Johnson, Lyndon, Statement at [Democratic] Luncheon, Statler Hotel [Hartford], 1960 September 9 (Box 700)
  - Jorgenson, A. N. (Box 700)
  - Judicial Conference of Magistrates, Trenton, 1959 November 13 (Box 700)
  - Kellems, Vivian (Box 700)
  - Keller, James (Father) (The Christophers), “The Twelve Ways to Strengthen Your Gov[ernmen]t” (Box 700)
  - Labor (Box 700)
  - Labor Council, [Third Constitutional Convention], 1959 September 10 (Box 700)
  - League of Women Voters, Inc[orporated] re: Candidates Questionnaire (Box 700)
  - Lee, Robert P. [Chair, State Development Commission] (Box 700)
  - Legislative Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 700)
  - Liquor Laws (Box 700)
  - Long Lane School for Girls – Middletown (Box 700)
  - Loughlin, Joseph M. (Fin[ance] Comm[issioner]) (Box 700)
  - Manufacturers Association of Conn[ecticut] 144th Annual Meeting (Box 700)
  - Massachusetts – Taxes (Box 700)
  - May, Edwin H. [Jr.] [Republican State Chair] (Box 700)
  - McGill, Ralph [Hartford Courant columnist] (Box 700)
  - Mental Health – Fairfield State Hospital (Box 700)
  - Mental Health – Naugatuck Valley Mental Health Marathon, 1958 June 20 (Box 700)
  - Mental Illness Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 700)
  - “Monitor,” NBC Interview, [Dave Garroway], 1957 April 28 (Box 700)
  - Motor Vehicles – Pallotti Case (Box 700)
  - Mulcahy, Leo J. [State Police Commissioner] (Box 700)
  - Murphy, [Associate] Justice James E. [State Supreme Court of Errors] (Box 700)
  - Murrow, Edward R. [Interview] (Box 700)
  - Natural Resources Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 700)
  - Nautilus Day, Friday, 1958 August 29 (Box 700)
  - National Civic Service League (Box 700)
  - Natural Resources (Box 700)
  - Navy Shore Patrols (New London, Conn[ecticut] Area) (Box 700)
  - Negro (Box 700)
  - New England Governors’ Conf[erence] Minutes and Agendas, 1959 March, November, 1960 June (Box 700)
  - New England Governors’ Conference, Stowe, Vermont, 1958 January 20 (Box 700)
  - New Haven [Mayor Richard C. Lee] (Box 700)
  - New Haven Assessors (Box 700)
  - New Haven Railroad – Ribicoff (Box 700)
  - New Haven Railroad Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 700)
  - New Year’s Safety Message (Box 700)
  - Norden Division (Box 700)
  - New York Mirror Youth Forum, 1959 December 5 (Box 700)
  - New York State Income Tax Law As It Affects Connecticut Residents (Box 700)
  - Nominating Speech by Mayor Lee, Democratic State Convention, 1958 June 28 (Box 700)
  - Olmstead, Alan, Articles [Columnist for Meriden Record] (Box 700)
  - Pan–American World Airways (Box 700)
  - Parole Board (Box 700)
  - Philosophy (Ribicoff) (Box 700)
  - Photographs [2 files transferred to “Ribicoff, Abraham” in Picture Group 500] (Box 700)
  - Political – Governor Ribicoff’s Speeches (Box 700)
  - Praise – Ribicoff (Box 700)
  - Presidential Mention (Box 700)
  - Press (Box 700)
  - Press Conferences, 1961 (Box 700)
  - Press Releases, 1959 (Box 700)
  - [Press Conferences & Press Releases], 1958-1960 (Box 701)
  - Public Law 875 [Federal Disaster Aid] (Box 701)
  - Radio [Recordings] (Box 701)
  - Recession – Baruch, Bernard N. (Box 701)
  - Recession – Federal Level (Box 701)
  - Recession – Ford, Norris (Remarks By) (Box 701)
  - Redevelopment – Hartford (Box 701)
  - Redevelopment Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 701)
  - Recreation Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 701)
  - Reflections on 1960 and What Will Be Important in 1961, Telephone Recorded by WCCC (Box 701)
  - Reflections on 1959 and What Will Be Important in 1960, Telephone Recorded WINF (Box 701)
  - Regional Planning (Box 701)
  - Religion (Box 701)
  - Religious Weekend (Box 701)
  - Rent Control (Box 701)
  - Reorganization Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 701)
  - Ribicoff Files, 1952-1959 (Box 701)
  - Right to Work (Box 701)
  - Rochambeau (Box 701)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box 701)
  - Sales Tax – Ruling by Supreme Court on Avco & Aircraft Industries (Box 701)
  - Schools (Box 701)
  - Seaside Sanatorium (Box 701)
  - Sex Deviates (Box 701)
  - Senatorial, 1956 (Box 701)
  - Shapiro, Bernard (Box 701)
  - Sherwood Island (Box 701)
  - Shore Erosion (Box 701)
  - Shore Erosion – Clippings and Editorials (Box 701)
  - Southbury Training School (Box 701)
  - Sports (Box 701)
  - Springfield Ordnance District (Box 701)
  - State Agencies Probe [Republican] (Box 701)
  - State Employees (Box 701)
  - State Employees – Travel (Box 701)
  - State Flood Control and Water Policy Commission (Box 701)
  - State Income Tax Speech by Governor Ribicoff [New York’s on Connecticut Residents] (Box 701)
  - State’s Mortgage Subsidy Program: 1 1/2% (Box 701)
  - State Office Building (Box 701)
  - Stone and Webster Service Corporation re: State of Conn[ecticut] Highway Department Organization Study, Summary of Report, 1957 (Box 701)
  - Tax Department re: Reorganization Report (Box 701)
  - Teachers’ Salaries (Box 701)
  - Teen–Agers (Slayings), [New Haven], 1956 May (Box 701)
  - Television (Box 701)
  - Textile Industry, Hartford, Conn[ecticut], 1958 September 22 (Box 701)
  - Traffic Safety Conference, Sacramento, [Address by Governor Ribicoff to 10th Annual Governors’ Traffic Safety Conference], 1959 October 8 (Box 701)
  - Transportation – New England Governors’ Conference (Box 701)
  - Tuberculosis & Other Chronic Illness, Comm[ission] on, re: Admission of Chronically Ill Patients to Cedarcrest and Laurel Heights, [Sanatoria], 1958 September 25 (Box 701)
  - Tucson, Arizona Speech [“Some Ideas on Highway Safety,” College of Business and Public Administration, University of Arizona, 1960 February 27 (Box 701)
  - Unemployment – Dev[elopment] Com[mission] Report[s], 1958 (Box 701)
  - United Aircraft Corporation – Sales Tax Refunds (Box 701)
  - United Press (Box 701)
  - University of Hartford (Box 701)
  - Urban Development (Box 701)
  - Vacation – Travel (Box 701)
  - Veterans (Box 701)
  - Vote – 18-year olds (Box 701)
  - Waldo, George Curtis (Box 701)
  - Welfare Dep[artmen]t – Survey by Conn[ecticut] Public Expenditure Council, 1957 (Box 701)
  - Yankee Expressway, Name for (Name for “Interstate 84 Highway”) (Box 701)
  - Youth (Box 701)
  - Zeller, Fred R. (State Comptroller) (Box 701)